<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on Blog - uTIcARdI</title><link>https://blog.gainskills.top/tags/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on Blog - uTIcARdI</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.gainskills.top/tags/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hugo-Customization</title><link>https://blog.gainskills.top/2019/02/06/hugo-customization/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.gainskills.top/2019/02/06/hugo-customization/</guid><description>A list about how I customize Hugo and why I did the change, the post will be updated continuously.
1. fractions Network Engineer should care about this, because it shows wrong IP/mask format with default value: fractions with default value Disable it in config.toml: [blackfriday] fractions = false
2. hrefTargetBlank This default value of the option is falsewhich means external links(The wording was corrected to &amp;ldquo;absolute&amp;rdquo; from &amp;lsquo;external&amp;rsquo; on Hugo official doc).</description></item><item><title>Hugo-Versioning</title><link>https://blog.gainskills.top/2019/01/27/hugo-versioning/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.gainskills.top/2019/01/27/hugo-versioning/</guid><description>Hugo provides the detail instructions about how to deploy it on different environment.
At first, I followed Deployment of Project Pages from /docs folder on master branch, and put all files in one repository.
I continue to check Deployment of Project Pages From Your gh-pages branch after I did some customization on hugo-theme-cleanwhite and want to publish the change to the forked branch.
Instead of follow Hugo guide, I did some try myself.</description></item><item><title>Hugo-Images management</title><link>https://blog.gainskills.top/2019/01/25/post-img-mgmt-hugo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.gainskills.top/2019/01/25/post-img-mgmt-hugo/</guid><description>I introduced why I migrate my blog to github and Hugo here. Most of articles have been moved to here in 30 days. Next, I just want to talk about something about posts&amp;rsquo; images management, versioning, theme customization/something about SEO.
Before start All images will be compressed before I upload them for post. There are many tools could do this, such as tinypng, UPNG. My choice is Tinypng because it supports variety formats and its API.</description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://blog.gainskills.top/2019/01/01/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.gainskills.top/2019/01/01/hello-world/</guid><description>Hello World!
Thanks
Hugo Git Page hugo-theme-cleanwhite I did some changes on the theme, will share it after testing. I spend days and finally get this Blog runs up. In next days, will move the posts from wordpress: hanbaobao2005.wordpress.com to here.
Happy Holidays :-)
Update at Jan-26-2019:
I have been running blogs for years, started at NetEase(NetEase shutdown its blog service at Nov-30-2018), then to Blogger(The blog was closed), and wordpress after Blogger was blocked within China.</description></item></channel></rss>